{
    "id": "aea0b06f8b4641759b82c62c78ae9471",
    "title": "Gap Fills",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Please don’t use your nail …………. a screwdriver.",
            "description": "We use ‘as’ to say what function a person or object has.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t like people …………… me in the middle of the night.",
            "description": "Like can be followed by an ing form or a to-infinitive.",
            "answers": [
                "to phone",
                "phoning",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I will let you …………….. my holiday dates next week.",
            "description": "Let is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "to know",
                "knowing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They kept watch all night lest the robbers ……………. come.",
            "description": "Should is the only auxiliary that can be used after lest.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am going to ………….. down for a few minutes.",
            "description": "To lie is to be horizontal.",
            "answers": [
                "lay",
                "lie",
                "lain"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I earn ………………. in my family.",
            "description": "The least is the superlative of little. It is used before uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "least",
                "the least",
                "fewest",
                "the fewest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Those who know the answer should ………….. their hands.",
            "description": "We use raise with an object.",
            "answers": [
                "raise",
                "rise",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………. from her seat.",
            "description": "To rise from your seat is to get up.",
            "answers": [
                "raised",
                "rose",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am very sure ……………… the test.",
            "description": "We use sure + infinitive  to talk about our own feelings.",
            "answers": [
                "to pass",
                "of passing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She seemed quite sure …………. the exam.",
            "description": "Sure + of + ing is used to refer to the feelings of the person you are talking about.",
            "answers": [
                "to pass",
                "of passing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am sorry ……………. my temper yesterday.",
            "description": "Sorry + about/for + ing is used to talk about past things we regret.",
            "answers": [
                "about losing",
                "for losing",
                "to lose"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am sorry …………… you that you failed the test.",
            "description": "Sorry + infinitive is used to apologize for current situations.",
            "answers": [
                "about telling",
                "for telling",
                "to tell"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}